Guide to the United Brewery Workers records, 1888-1977 IBT0003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- General Correspondence Microfilm, 1911-1947; Series 4
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #92, 1941 October; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 35)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #93, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 35)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #93, 1935 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 35)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #93, 1934 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 36)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #94, 1947 December; Series 4
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #96, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 36)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #96, 1937 December 3; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 36)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #96, 1936 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 36)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #96, 1935 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 37)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #97, 1939 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 37)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #98, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 37)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #98, 1937 July; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 37)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #98, 1937 June; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 38)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #99, 1922 November; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 38)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #102, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 38)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #102, 1944 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 38)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #102, 1943 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 39)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #104, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 39)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #104, 1936 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 39)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #105, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 39)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #105, 1941 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 39)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #105, 1940 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 40)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #107, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 40)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #109, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 40)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #109, 1944 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 40)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #109, 1936 February; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 40)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #109, 1935 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 41)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #110, 1938 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 41)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #111, 1942 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 41)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #111, 1939 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 41)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #111, 1913 April; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 41)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #112, 1932 June; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 42)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #114, 1937 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 42)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #115, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 42)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #115, 1941 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 42)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #115, 1936 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 42)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #115, 1935 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 43)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #116, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 43)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #118, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 43)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #121, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 43)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #121, 1942 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 43)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #121, 1941 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 44)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #122, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 44)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #122, 1938 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 44)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #122, 1934 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 44)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #122, 1934 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 44)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #122, 1933 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 45)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #123, 1943 September; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 45)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #126, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 45)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #127, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 45)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #127, 1945 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 45)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #127, 1944 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 46)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #129, 1938 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 46)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #130, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 46)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #130, 1942 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 46)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #130, 1940 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 46)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #130, 1939 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 47)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #130, 1935 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 47)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #132, 1942 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 47)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #133, 1944 November; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 47)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #133, 1943 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 47)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #133, 1942 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 48)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #133, 1937 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 48)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #134, 1912 August; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 48)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #136, 1941 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 48)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #137, 1911 November; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 48)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #138, 1945 July; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 49)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #139 (Paper) Kankauna, Wisconsin, 1947 September; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 49)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #141, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 49)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #142, 1945 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 49)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #142 Walla Walla, Washington, 1943; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 49)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #142, 1942 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 50)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #142, 1939 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 50)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #142, 1937 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 50)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #142, 1935 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 50)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #142, 1935 April; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 50)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #142, 1935 March; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 51)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #142, 1933 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 51)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #144, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 51)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #144, 1935 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 51)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #148, 1946 October; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 51)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #148, 1942 August; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 52)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #149, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 52)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #149, 1936 November; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 52)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #150, 1940 July; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 52)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #150, 1936 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 52)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #150, 1935 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 53)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #151, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 53)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #152, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 53)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #153, 1939 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 53)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #153, 1938 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 53)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #153, 1937 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 54)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #155, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 54)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #156, Local Union #157, 1920 January; 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 54)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #158, 1946 October; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 54)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #158, 1933 August; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 54)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #159, 1942 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 55)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #161, 1943 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 55)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #162, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 55)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #163, 1945 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 55)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #163, 1942 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 55)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #163, 1941 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 56)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #163, 1933 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 56)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #164, Local Union #165, 1942 July; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 56)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #166, 1935 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 56)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #166, 1934 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 57)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #171, 1946 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 57)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #171, 1940 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 57)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #173, 1947 November; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 57)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #174, 1944 January; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 57)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #174, 1943 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 58)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #174, 1935 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 58)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #176, 1939 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 58)
  - SUb-roll 4: Local Union #178, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 58)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #178, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 19, Reel 58)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #178, 1941 January; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 59)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #181, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 59)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #182, 1937 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 59)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #182, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 59)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #183, 1921 January; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 59)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #185, 1947, December (Box 20, Reel 60)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #186, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 60)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #186, 1940 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 60)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #186, 1933 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 60)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #187, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 61)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #188, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 61)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #188, 1941 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 61)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #188, 1939 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 61)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #188, 1934 May; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 61)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #191, Local 193, Local 194, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 62)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #195, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 62)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #196, 1943 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 62)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #196, 1938 June; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 62)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #196, 1938 May; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 63)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #197, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 63)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #198, 1937 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 63)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #199, 1947 October; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 63)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #200, 1940 January; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 63)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #200, 1939 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 64)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #201, 1934 January; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 64)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #205, 1945 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 64)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #205, 1941 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 64)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #205, 1940 January; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 64)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #205, 1939 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 65)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #205, 1933 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 65)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #206, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 65)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #208, 1947 October; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 65)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #209, 1933 September; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 65)
  - Sub-roll 1: Local Union #210, 1944 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 66)
  - Sub-roll 2: Local Union #212, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 66)
  - Sub-roll 3: Local Union #215, 1947 October; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 66)
  - Sub-roll 4: Local Union #217, 1947 December; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 66)
  - Sub-roll 5: Local Union #217, 1934 September; Series 4 (Box 20, Reel 66)
- The Brewery Worker Newspapers, 1936-1973; Series 5
  This series consists of copies of the Golden Anniversary edition of the Brewery Worker, 1936, and a bound volume of the Brewery Worker, 1972-1973.
  This eries is arranged by item: The Brewery Worker Golden Anniversary issue and the Brewery Worker bound volume.
  - The Brewery Worker Magazine, Vol 87-88 (Book Format), 1972-1973; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - The Brewery Worker Golden Anniversary Edition, Vol. LI, No.35 (16 Copies), August 29, 1936; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Local 222 Records, 1967-2004; Series 6
  This series consist of materials relating to United Brewery Workers Local 222 such as minutes, reports, correspondence and a contract.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Labor negotiations; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century
  - Finance Reports, 1970-1973; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Frman and Schmidt Brewing Company Pension Plan, 1974; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Local 222 Checkbook, 1970-1975; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Local No. 222 Meeting Minutes, October 10, 1968; Series 6 (Box SHARED Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1967-1975; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1968-1972; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Strategic Planning Meeting Folder, 2004; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters Merger Correspondence, 1972-1974; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 3)